[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This great boxer, known as the Galveston Giant, was the worlds Heavyweight Champion from 1908-1915.", "correct_answer": "Jack Johnson", "incorrect_answers": ["Jim Jeffries", "Jim Johnson", "Jack Jeffries"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A variation of what color is the shade called Harlequin?", "correct_answer": "Green", "incorrect_answers": ["Blue", "Orange", "Red"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the 1991 movie with this tagline:  In every neighborhood there is a house that adults whisper about and children cross the street to avoid.", "correct_answer": "The People Under the Stairs", "incorrect_answers": ["Nightmare on Elmstreet", "The Haunted House of Horror", "The Last House on the Left"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ladino is a language composed of  which two other languages ?", "correct_answer": "Hebrew and Spanish", "incorrect_answers": ["Spanish and Portuguese", "Spanish and Arabic", "Portuguese and Italian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this part of the world tattooing has been a common practice since antiquity. Featuring elaborate geometrical figures, tattoos were a natural artistic design on the skin of their owner.", "correct_answer": "Polynesia", "incorrect_answers": ["Indonesia", "Malaysia", "The Middle East"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which was the first country in the world to constitutionally abolish its army?", "correct_answer": "Costa Rica", "incorrect_answers": ["Gabon", "Togo", "Estonia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is referred to as the solar apex?", "correct_answer": "the direction the Sun travels through space", "incorrect_answers": ["the highest point the Sun reaches during the day", "the warmest day of the year as measured on the equator", "the highest UV reading taken from the earths surface"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The national motto of what country is Peace at Home, Peace in the World?", "correct_answer": "Turkey", "incorrect_answers": ["Afghanistan", "Somalia", "Nigeria"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long did it take to film The Blair Witch Project?", "correct_answer": "8 days", "incorrect_answers": ["3 days", "3 weeks", "1 week"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The show Mad Money aired CNBC cable/satellite TV channel on Monday, March 14, 2005 with what host?", "correct_answer": "Jim Cramer", "incorrect_answers": ["Joel Kramer", "Jack Aronsohn", "Jim Aronsohn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When Stella Adler returned to the USA she began teaching with this famous theater group.", "correct_answer": "Group Theater", "incorrect_answers": ["Guthrie Theater", "Yale Drama School", "The Northwestern School of Drama"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Haley Joel Osment played Forrest Gumps son in the popular movie.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]